

kripajoshi45@gmail.com | C: 647-614-6520 | Woodstock, ON N4T 0M1

### Summary

Self-driven motivated individual with outstanding dedication and great problem solving abilities. Trustworthy, Hard working, Adaptability, Willingness to learn and excellent Timekeeper. Knowledgeable and experienced in Computer based records management systems. Good understanding of accounting software systems, Microsoft office package and administrative works.

#### Skills

- MS Word
- MS Excel
- MS Powerpoint
- Email and communication
- Tally (Accounting software)
- Finsys (Accounting software)
- Navigator (Accounting software)

- Advanced computer proficiency (With Diploma in Web development)
- Analytical reasoning
- Flexible team player
- Time management
- Planning skill
- Hard working
- Problem solving skill

# Experience

Internship at WDDTechnologies. | 18 Carlton Drive Orangeville, Ontario, L9W 2X9

Web developer (intern)

09/2021 - 01/2022

- Consulted and worked for a client of WDDTechnologies, named "Phoenix Mates".
- During this period, I was asked to create a clone of https://esqido.com/ (ecommerce) site.
- I was responsible for creating whole end-to-end solution for the site, from frontend, backend, and admin.
- Frontend and admin was created in ReactJs, with sass for styling.
- Backend was created in NestJs, and mysql was used for database.

Kathmandu, Nepal Accountant

07/2016 - 06/2019

- MM International Pvt Ltd | Rabibhawan, Consolidate various accounting statements reports.
  - Preparing income balance sheet statements, Day book and Book Keeping.
  - Reconciliation accounts receivable records from the bills and make sure cash was successfully collected and receipts were properly recorded.
  - Daily Follow up for the payment of the customers and remainder them by telecomunication or mailing.
  - Responsible for reviewing as well as verifying the accuracy of journal entries accounting classifications assigned to various records.

Nepal

**Software Quality Assurance Tester** 01/2015 - 06/2016

- Technomax | Shorakhutte, Kathmandu, Test software to ensure that high quality is maintained.
  - Also handled day to day office management activities

Yala Multipurpose Co-operative Ltd | Saugal, Kathmandu, Nepal

**Junior Assistant** 12/2011 - 01/2015

- Maintain daily accounting transactions and updating the accounting software.
- Handling the cash transaction of the company.
- Preparing all the vouchers.
- Involve in preparing the cash report.
- Loan disbursement and handling payment maintenance.
- Shares issues and accounts works.

Surya Multipurpose Co-operative Ltd | Putalisadak, Kathamandu, Nepal **Accounting Assistant** 

06/2010 - 10/2011

- Assist in Data Posting.
- Data entry in Accounting Software.
- Help customers with deposits and withdrawals.
- Validation and verification of books.
- Maintain daily Accounting Vouchers, day book, Book-keeping.
- Preparing Balance sheet, Income and Expenditure, Cash Statement.

# **Education and Training**

TriOS COLLEGE | Mississauga, ON Enterprise Web & Mobile Development (Diploma, passed with Distinction) 09/2020 - 01/2022

Unique College Of Management | Kumaripati, Lalitpur, Nepal **BBS** in Bussiness Studies 03/2005 - 03/2009

#### Certifications

- Tally 9.0
- DOS
- MS Word
- MS Excel
- MS Power Point
- Internet and Email